James Bramble

Lifelong seeker of knowledge and a Business graduate who currently has his sights set on a full-time web development position. Experience in HTML5, CSS3, Javascript, jQuery, Bootstrap, Materialize, Firebase, and Node.js. Knowledgeable in all aspects of business management and development.

15295 S. Sturgeon Dr.
Olathe, KS 66062
(913) 620-8394
jbramble.rls@gmail.com
www.linkedin.com/in/ibramble18

EXPERIENCE

R. L. Schreiber, Kansas City Metro — Independent Purveyor

April 2011 - Present

Independent purveyor responsible for building sales and maintaining relationships with customers in the food service industry.

EVCO Wholesale Foods, Emporia, KS — *Marketing Advisor*

December 2009 - April 2011

Marketing advisor charged with building relationships with customers to help them build their business and improve their bottom-line.

PB&J Robin LLC, Overland Park — General Manager

March 2006 - August 2009

Held full management authority for a 3 million per year business. Supervised a staff of over 70 hourly employees, 5 managers, ensuring customer service and quality standards were met at every level.

EDUCATION

MidAmerica Nazarene University, Olathe, KS — BA Applied Organizational Leadership

2015

University of Kansas, Overland Park — Full Stack Web Development Certification

November 2018 - May 2019

Completed a rigorous 24 week Full Stack Web Development Bootcamp

TECHNICAL SKILLS

Node.JS, Express, JavaScript, jQuery, React.js, GIT, Github, Mongo DB, MySQL, Firebase, HTML, CSS, Bootstrap, APIs, JSON, AJAX, computer science fundamentals

AWARDS

Winner of most socially conscious app design for "See and Say" project

Winner of 2 National Sales contests in 2017 for increasing sales and creating new accounts.

Winner of National Sales contest for increasing year over year sales.

PROJECTS

See and Say

A speech therapy tool designed to help young children gain access to a app designed to improve speech and communication skills

jbramble18.github.io/See-and -Say